继   承   之   战
第 4 季  第 9 集
阻止大选结果认证
...to prevent this certification of election results
直到所有邮寄选票计算完成
until all absentee ballots are tallied
同时 希门尼斯的支持者
Meanwhile, Jimenez supporters are making their voices heard
也在多处进行示威
in a number of demonstrations around the country
包括 在泛美网科的曼哈顿办公室
including outside the Manhattan offices of ATN
泛美网科率先 宣布了杰瑞德·门肯当选的消息
who first called the election for Jeryd Mencken.
大批愤怒的示威者
Crowds of angry protestors
持续前往泛美网科总部
continue to make their way towards ATN's headquarters.
因为传出多起暴力和胁迫事件
With reports of a number of instances of street violence and intimidation
纽约警察局呼呼民众 为了安全…
NYPD is urging the public for their own safety.
家父 洛根·罗伊
My father, Logan Roy, was a great man
是个不折不扣的伟人
in the true sense of the word
他在家中 三个小孩里 排行老二
Born the middle child of three
二战期间 被送往外地
he was sent away during the Second World War
以… 叽里呱啦…
To… bing bang bong
悲伤…
Sad...
我好帅 真的好帅
I look good, I look good
我是老大 老大就是我
I am the man, I am the man.
成如各位所见 我在这里
As you can see, here I am
大声地谈论我父亲的事情
talking loudly about my father
各位不觉得 我有一点点像他吗
And don't I, perhaps, remind you of him, just a little?
有点干
A little dry.
芝加哥日报 1981年
Chicago Daily,'81
成立了"报道者”
Launches The Correspondent
对人类沟通的热情
A passion for human communication
我是鸟王
am King Dong
我是大鸟之王
I am the King of Dong
向我敬礼吧
Bow down to me.
总统是我挑的
I selected the President.
他的要害被我捏在手上
Do you see his pecker in my pocket?
第一次婚姻宣告破裂 好伤心...
End of the first marriage, it's very sad, saddy, sad, sad.
小心
Look out.
看小西哭泣 看肯尼说谎…
See Shivvy cry, see Kenny lie..
还有大表演家罗曼 照亮天空
see Roman the Showman light up the sky
最后的时日 新的冒险
Last days, new adventures
他会不会是...小小声地说 有点失去理智了?
Was he, may be, tiny, nice voice, losing it a little?
天晓得 但他确实是个伟人
Who knows? But a great man.
他过世的消息 像野火般传开
His demise was carried, written in fire
像电光般地脉动 如同闪光
pulsed electric in a flash
传遍七大洲
over seven continents
通过他创办的报纸
into newspapers that he started
他建立的网络
networks he launched
他铺设的光纤
through fiber he laid
我们建造的卫星
satellites we built
他确实是个伟人
A great man indeed
一个非常伟大的人
A great, great man.
父亲 我可以吗
Father, with your permission?
请大家鼓掌 热烈鼓掌
Applause all around. Come on, let her rip.
我们爱你
We love you.
再说些废话…
Something.
什么事  -罗曼 嘿 兄弟 你好吗
What's up?   -Rome, hey, man. You okay?
是 很好 我很好
Yeah. I'm okay. I'm good
老实说 我很兴奋
I'm actually, like... Honestly, I'm excited
这样会很变态吗
Does that make me a sick fuck?
门肯胜选 他阻止我们的交易
Mencken wins, he blocks the deal
这是令人兴奋的时代 是很有意思的时代
It's, you know, it's exciting times, interesting times
你觉得 基于商业和其他考量
Do you think, you know, for business, for everything...
要不要让杰瑞德稍微收敛点?
can we may be get Jerryd to turn the volume down a little?
拜托 别这么尬 老哥
Oh, come on. Don't be a pussy, dude
怎么 你不喜欢这样的收视率吗
What, you don't like these fucking ratings?
这是冲突
It's discord, man.
冲突让我性欲勃发
Discord makes my dick "hord.
当然 但…
Sure. Just...
毕竟这是葬礼
I mean, it is the funeral
他一定会喜欢的 你在开什么玩笑
Oh, he'd fucking love it. Are you kidding me?
其实 我也不知道 我只是觉得...不太好
You know, I don't know. Just a little Queasy Gonzales?
对...我们都很忙 我们在小西家见 对吧
Yeah... We're all busy. Okay. We'll see you at Shiv sky's, right?
好 嘿 罗曼 我们…在那边见
Okay. Hey, Rome, I'll... I'll see you there.
好  -我挺你
Okay.   -Roll deep
嘿  -嘿 肯 我只想说 我很担心
Hey.   -Hey, Ken. Listen, I... I just want to say that I am concerned, okay?
大家都说 今天会有大动乱
Everybody's saying that there's gonna be
谢谢  -没事 拉瓦 那都是谣言
Thank you.   -No, yeah. Rava, that's... that's rumors.
我坐费克雷的车
Okay, I'm with Fikret.
我会跟弟弟妹妹一起过去 但他会去接你们
I'm gonna go with the sibs, but he'll pick you guys up and.
不要 肯 听我说 我想…
Okay. Yeah, no. Ken, listen, I think we may…
我们今天要去上州
I think we're gonna head up state today
什么  -很抱歉
What?   -And I'm... I'm really sorry
但我已经决定了
but that is... that is my decision, okay?
我们要去找崔维斯和罗伯特…
We're gonna go to Travis and Robert's...
你在说什么啊
What are you even talking about?
肯 我觉得 今天很不安全
Ken, it... it just... It does not feel safe today, okay?
这是我们必须要做的事 好吗
This is just what we need to do, all right?
你现在在哪里 在路上吗
Where are you now? Are you... are you on the road?
你们已经出发了吗  -还没有 但...
Have you left yet?   -No, we haven't left, but we're...
费克雷 三分钟后到拉瓦家
Fikret, I wanna be at Rava's in three minutes, okay?
违章和罚款我负责 总之 我要马上到
I'll figure out fines and violations. Just get us there now.
真是惨不忍赌 对吧
What a shit show, huh?
你在看吗  -对 我在
Okay, are you watching?   -Yeah, yeah.
我想 你该公布你的假数据
I reckon you should get your bad numbers out
看来 今天会是掩埋坏消息的好日子
because it's just become an amazing day to bury bad news.
对吧  -我不确定耶
Yeah?   -I don't know.
就好比 如果老二很小的话
Like, if you have a little dicky
最好不要去裸体海滩
maybe you don't go to the nudist beach?
卢卡斯  -怎样
Lukas.   -Yeah?
现在 有一波毁天灭地的海啸
A tsunami just came and washed everything away
不会有人看你的小老二…
No one is checking the dicks. Just...
真的 这是我最懂的事 你公布就是了 昭告天下
Seriously, I know this. Do it. Get them out.
你好蛮横  -对
You're so forceful.   -Yeah.
要怎么避开门肯
Well, how do we get around Mencken?
因为 这是真的吧
'Cause this... this is real, right?
他要用法规刁难这笔交易
That he's blocking the deal over regulatory.
我觉得不可能
Well, I don't... I still don't see it
你知道他…
You know, he's...
他违背了国内某些根深蒂固的想法
He's out of tune with some... some deep sentiments in this country.
你们实行民主体制才50年...
Yeah, well, you've been a democracy for, like, 50 years, so...
什么 不是 我是说… 好吧
What? No, I mean... Well, okay.
除非 你不把黑人算在内
No, not unless you don't count black people
不过 这是个坏习惯 所以…
which is kind of a bad habit, so you...
你说得对 但是 情况比较复杂
Okay, yes, but it's a little more complicated than that.
我只是说
I'm just... I'm just saying
你们的民主体制几乎跟博淡瓦纳一样成熟
You... you are nearly as mature a democracy as Botswana.
所以 我该找人帮忙  这要怎么做啊
So, I should reach out. How did that go, by the way?
我还是觉得 最利落的做法就是 直接行动
I... I still think cleanest is just activate.
你能不能去找你兄弟 让算法
Can you talk to your buddies and... and get the algo
直接换上真数据
you know, pushing that straight dope?
明白了吗 我得走了
You know? All right, well, I gotta go.
但他今天会到场的 知道吗
But he's gonna be there today. Yeah?
叫艾芭趁乱掩埋假数据
So, get Ebba to bury those numbers
现在是好机会
It's just so golden.
你在做什么 你以为你在干吗
What are you doing? What do you think you're doing?
肯 肯
Ken, Ken.
肯 你做什么  -这他妈是怎么回事
Ken, what are you doing?   -What the fuck is going on?
我们只是要出城
We are just getting out of town
你们要...你这是歇斯底里的疯话
You're getting... Well, that's hysterical bullshit
你不让孩子们…
Okay? You're not... you're not bringing the kids
参加爷爷的葬礼 你疯了吗
to their grandfather's funeral? Are you insane?
我觉得不安全
I don't consider it safe
你上网上太多了
You're... you're too online.
好吗 你跟现实脱节了
Okay? You've lost context.
一切都很好
Everything is fine
没有一件事是好的
Nothing is fine.
你说过 一切都会没事 你说过丹尼尔会赢
You said things would be okay. You said that Daniel would win.
我们的女儿很不好 你们不能走
Our daughter is not fine. You can't go.
一切都很不好 你不... 你们不能走  -让开
Nothing is fine. You don't...  You can't go.  -Get out of my way.
今天不要惹我
Do not fuck with me today.
肯...  -今天不要惹我
Ken...   -Do not fuck with me today
你必须停一下 必须冷静下来
You need to stop. You need to calm down
肯  -嘿 孩子们 苏菲 开门
Ken, Ken...   -Hey, guys. Soph? Open up
肯 没事
Ken. It's okay
肯 你必须停下 你必须停下
Ken, you've got to stop this. You've gotta stop.
你必须停下 我觉得去那里不安全
You've gotta stop. I do not consider it safe.
好吗  -放屁 都是借口
Okay?   -That's bullshit. Pretext.
你想伤害我
You're trying to hurt me.
今天他妈的是我爸的葬礼  -我真的很抱歉 好吗
It's my fucking father's funeral.   -I'm really sorry, okay?
但我们要走了 我们会去参加追悼会
But we are gonna go. And there will be a memorial.
他说不办追悼会
He didn't want a memorial.
我要去法院
I'm gonna go to court
申请紧急禁令 不让你们出城
to get an emergency court order to stop you leaving the city
我就要这样做  -好 你去吧
That's what I'm gonna do.   -Okay. Go do that
好吗
Okay?
我要挡住你的车
I'm gonna block your car.
我要躺在你的车前面
I'm gonna lie in front of your fucking car.
想出城的话 得碾过我才行
Okay? You're gonna have to run me over if you wanna go.
你打算怎么做
What are you gonna do?
时间线是谁给他们的?
Who... So, who gave them the timeline?
很多人都知道
Well, a lot of people know.
很多人不想因为战争罪 被送去海牙
A lot of people don't wanna go to The Hague for war crimes.
瞧你
Look at you.
我的版面不多
Well, there's not much of me, you know?
达温的照片好大一张
There's a great big graphic of Darwin.
这减少了我的重要性
I think that this diminishes my role.
我反正已经被门肯的事情玷污…
I'm tarred with the Mencken brush
不如趁机捞一票 对吧
So I might, may as well get my goodies, right?
若拿不到别墅 入党就没什么意义了
There's no point joining the party unless you get your little dacha.
我说两分钟
I said two minutes.
我明明说了两分钟 谢谢
I did say two minutes. Thank you
干嘛
What?
没事 没事 我只是…
No, no. I just.
葬礼 对吧 我是说
The funeral, right? I mean,
我觉得 必须画下句点
I feel the need for closure.
我想好好地哀悼… 我想…
I would like to grieve, I would like to.
我也是 我也是 我要扶棺
Oh, I do, I do, too. I do, too. I'm a wheelman.
我是扶棺人 在右前方
I'm a casket wheelman. I'm front right
这...
It's
好 好 滚吧
Fine, fine. Fuck off
滚吧 快滚  -谢谢
Fuck off. Go on.   -Thank you.
帮我留个位子 留一个好位子
Save me a place, though. A good place.
好吧 第二排
Okay? Second row.
告诉门肯的团队 我是当初做决策的人
And tell the Mencken team that I made the call, okay?
告诉门肯 是我决定宣布他胜选
Tell Mencken that I swung it for him.?
你干脆用走的吧 因为堵车了
And you may as well walk 'cause it's gridlock
现在可以进来了 谢谢
Okay, now come in. Thank you
你好啊
Hello.
派对时间到
Party time.
你来了
There you are.
门肯今天会来吗
Is he gonna come today? Mencken?
马特森呢
Is Mats son?
看来他不懂得认赔杀出 你应该高兴才对
Doesn't know when he's beat. You should be pleased
门肯赢了 交易告吹 我们可以继续当家
Mencken wins, blocks the deal, we stay in charge
是 你当家
Yeah. You do.
是”我们家”掌权
Well, the idea is family, so..
你要看大局
Big picture, yeah.
对 今天真是个天杀的好日子
Yep, it's just a great fucking day
你还好吗
You okay?
对 对 我很好
Yeah. Yeah, good.
我不知道
I don't know.
拉瓦要带孩子们出城
Rava's taking the kids out of the city
她很担心 所以...
She's concerned, so..
这真是又蠢又过份
Well, that's dumb and shitty
我很遗憾 肯
I'm sorry, Ken.
是啊...
Yeah. Well.
没关系 反正也没办法 对吧
It's fine. It is what it is, right?
妈妈有没有邀请你们 参加“加勒比海净空活动”?
You guys get Mom's invitation for a " Caribbean air clear "?
妈突然有兴趣当妈了吗
Oh, Mom just suddenly wants to Mom now?
对 我不去
Yeah, I'm a hard no.
对  -是啊
Right.   -Yeah.
我应该告诉你们
I should tell you
因为 我今天可能会告诉妈妈
cause I'm telling Mom today, probably, so.
其实 我早就想告诉你们
I've wanted to say for a while
我其实...怀孕了
I'm actually... I'm pregnant
现在你们知道了
There you go.
是我的吗  -对
Is it mine?   -Yeah.
真的吗 天啊 小西
Really? Fuck. Shiv.
还有...
And...
对 是汤姆的 不...
Yeah, it's Tom's. Not..
很好  -真要命
Good.   -Fuck's sake.
对  -恭喜
Yeah.   - Congratulations.
你要生威姆士丹的小孩
Yeah, you're having a Wambs gland.
我还以为你都是靠吃乐西宣泄感情
I thought you'd just been eating your feelings
是啊 谢了 你真会说
Yeah. Thanks. Good stuff
你知道 我会一直开玩笑
You know I'm not gonna stop with the joke things.
还有 如果被我看到 你喂母乳
I'm also, like, if I see you breastfeeding
我会打手枪的
am gonna have to jerk off
我的老天爷啊  -因为 那场面会很火辣
Jesus fucking Christ, man.   -I... I mean that because it will be hot.
你知道你有多恶心吗  -喜欢吗
Do you know how disgusting you are?   -Do you love it?
不要  -要再搞一次吗
No.   -Should we bone again?
不...去你的  -生个老二?
No... fuck off.   -Kid number two?
两位 今天能不能…
Guys, can... can we..
我们能不能看在葬礼的份上
Today, shall we, for the funeral, just..
稍微收敛一下  -为了葬礼而休战
Yeah? Cool it?   -Like a funeral truce.
对 今天就不要扯别的了
Yeah, like, today is just about today
嘿 杰西 我手机开扩音了
Hey, Jess, you're on speaker.
好 我听说 好像有某个聚会
Listen, so, they're... they're saying that there's, like, a... a gathering
似乎是从公园出发的游行
or like a... like a march or something...that's gathering from the park
罗斯福快速路 塞得动弹不得
and FDR's like, totally gridlocked
你们要不要 我...
so, do you want me to just
等一下
Oh, wait.
我发个定位 我能给你们指路
I dropped a pin. I can guide you
是啊
Yeah.
嗨 早安  -早安
Hi. Good morning.   -Good morning.
你还好吗  -好得很
How you doing?   -Fine. Great. Swell.
今天是个好日子  -是啊
Great day.   -Yeah.
我想 从上城区走比较容易
So, yeah, I think from uptown, it's easier
但是 路上很乱 所以...
but there's just, like, a lot of confusion, so.
你戴墨镜 真聪明 可以偷偷地哭
Glasses, that's smart. You can cry in secret.
隐藏所有情绪
Hide all your emotions
成为葬礼上的胜利者
and thus emerge victorious as the winner of the funeral.
嘿 杰西 听我说  -好
Hey, Jess, listen.   -Yeah.
下星期初...  -好
Early next week...   -Okay.
我要 跟几个家庭律师 谈谈
I wanna speak with some family lawyers.
我要争取监护权
Custody. I want custody.
好  -好吗
Okay.   -Okay?
星期一 星期二 排在….
Monday, Tuesday. Let's do.
好的
All right.
这是什么 为什么要跟你开会?
What's this? What's this meet with you?
这个不重要 只是…
Oh, don't worry about that. Just...
好 这个取消  -好
Okay. But let's... let's bump that.   -Yeah
所以 这是要干吗
So... So, what is it? What is this?
到时候再谈吧
Yeah, shall we just do it when we do it?
这是要谈什么
Like, what is it?
我只是想谈我的...情况
I just wanna talk about my... situation
好 没问题
Okay. Sure.
你的情况怎样  -肯 今天是大日子
What about your situation?   -Ken, this is a big day
我不想在今天谈
I don't wanna do this today.
你害我开始胡思乱想了
Yeah, well, now I'm thinking, like, all kinds of things.
说嘛 到底是什么事
So, come on. What?
这个… 你一直都很支持我  -对
Well, you have always been so supportive of me -Yeah.
支持我的目标和抱负 我真的很感谢你
and my aims and ambitions and I really appreciate that
所以 我想 你应该能够理解
So, I'm sure that you can understand
现在 是我转换跑道的好时机
that it might be a good time for me to move on to another position
好 好
Okay. Okay.
没问题 当然没问题
Fine. Fine. Of course. Of course, you can.
太好了
Great.
我们到时候可以多聊一些...
Yeah, and we can chat more about it when we...
我可以问问原因吗
Can I ask why?
我就觉得…
Yeah. It just..
时候到了
feels like time, you know?
是因为门肯吗
Is this about Mencken?
其实 我已经考虑一阵子了
Well, I've been thinking about it for a while, so...
好 好  -对不起
Fine, fine.   -I'm sorry.
好
Yeah
我只想说…
I just have to say, like, like.
这样很荒谬 杰西
It's, like, kinda... it's kind of ridiculous, Jess, though
如果你觉得过意不去
I mean, if you feel sorry about it
也许应该再考虑一下
maybe you should reconsider.
我只是觉得 时候到了
I just think that it's time.
对不起 但我给了你不可多得的机会
I'm sorry, but I've... I've given you extraordinary access.
还有哪里能让你这样?
Where else are you gonna get that?
没有别的地方了
Nowhere.
我告诉你 没有别的地方会这样
I'm telling you, you're gonna get that nowhere
你不知道事情的结局会是如何
You have no idea how things will turn out
这样很幼稚
and it's very juvenile
这样很蠢 你真的很蠢
It's fucking dumb. You're being dumb
所有人都蠢透了
Everybody's being fucking dumb
很遗憾你这样想 肯德尔
Okay, sorry you feel that way, Kendall
杰西 你真的很会选时间 挑今天告诉我
Nice timing, Jess. Lovely day to tell me.
实在太体贴了
Really thoughtful.
肯 GoJo
Ken. GoJo.
马特森说漏嘴
Mats son has slipped out
说他们在南亚的订阅数目
that they've got deeply bullshit subscriber numbers
严重作假
all across South Asia.
那个现在先不说
But that's not for now.
但 你现在告诉我了 不是吗
Well, you are, in fact, telling me now, right?
对 只是让你知道 你现在不用处理
Yeah, but it's not for you to engage. It's just.. just so you know.
今天的天气还算好
Weather could have been a lot worse for this, huh?
这是...我以为我们...
Okay, well, this is... I thought that we were gonna..
康 致悼词的人是罗曼
Roman was doing the eulogy, Con
但我们说过 如果要的话 可以考虑
But we said we could consider, if we wanted to.
是 没错 当然
Yeah. Sure.
但是 这篇好长 而且很难懂
But this is long, and it's hard to follow.
对 这在形式上很有独创性
Right, well, it's formally inventive.
是我们最喜欢的特点
That's one of the things that we like most about it
对 但我觉得 这段悼词会害我们吃上官司
Okay, well, I think this eulogy's gonna leave us open to legal action
好 你打了谁
All right, so who have you hit?
我打了谁?  -对
Who have I hit?   -Yeah.
好吧 就是...
Okay. Well, just, you know.
因为我觉得这很棒 门肯有种族歧视
because I think it's great that Mencken's a racist
不愿让肮脏的外国人买我们公司
and he won't let a dirty foreigner buy the company
但我还是觉得 应该让董事会
but I still think we need to-get the board and brass
和公司高层 支持我们这些孤儿
rallying around the old orphans here, don't you think?
当然了 对 当然了
Sure. Yeah, sure, dude
那好
Okay.
玛西娅今天打扮好时髦 秀色可餐
Marcia's look in'chic. Yummy
她是个性感寡妇
She's a sexy funeral lady
如果你这样就吓到了
If you're weirded out by that
等我跟她在老爸棺材上做爱 吓死你
wait'til I have sex with her on Dad's coffin
真他妈奇怪
It's so fuckin'weird
悼词写得不错 对吧 他写得很好
The eulogy is good, right? He did good?
对 他如鱼得水
Yeah. He's on top of the world
在一个 到都是目标的环境中
Target-rich environment,
大家不是虚情假意 就是一脸衰戚
glad-handing the sad faces
天啊
Oh, man.
圣殿里好多兑换银钱之人
So many fucking money-changers in the temple
嘿 他在那里
Hey, there he is
弗兰克 我只想说 我知道 我们过去有过不和
Frank, just wanna say I know we've had our battles and such
但 在死亡之前 一切都不再那么重要 是吧
but this really puts it in perspective, don't it?
当然 人生苦短 我们应该和睦相处
Sure. Life is short. We should all love one another.
对  -有话就说吧
Right.   -Go on.
没事 我…
Nothing. Just..
只是发现一件事
Just an observation
门肯会阻止这笔交易
Mencken is going to block the deal
如果 肯失去战斗意志
And if Ken has lost his stomach for the fight
我真的希望他没有
which I really hope he hasn't
蛋糕上会有一颗樱桃
if there's gonna be one cherry on the cake
我会…你知道的…我会招兵买马
well, I'll be, you know, rounding up a posse.
好的 跟你聊得很开心
Okay. Well, lovely chatting
你被两个小人缠住了
Yeah, you are tied to two dirty little fuckers.
嘿 嘿 罗曼  -格雷格瑞
Hey, hey, Rome.   -Gregory.
嘿 真是悲伤的一天  -对啊
Hey. Sad day. Sad day.   -Oh, yeah, yeah
谢了  -门肯在那里
Thanks.   -So... so, Mencken's right there.
对 我知道
Yeah, I know. I'm aware.
对  -可以帮我介绍一下吗
Yeah.   -So, can you get me an intro?
介绍你 给门肯认识?  -对
To Mencken?   -Yeah.
你能不能...我是说...我曾是
Can you... I mean, I'm... I'm one of the... I was one of..
我是加冕委员会的成员 所以...
I'm amongst the crowning committee, so..
对 也许晚一点吧
Right, okay. Yeah, may be. Later
你负责盯着尤恩 行吗
You're on Ewan watch, okay?
他想上台讲话
He wanted to speak
可惜时间不够
but unfortunately, there was no time
所以 如果他开始拉白布条
so if he starts, like, unfurling a banner
或唱工会之歌
or, you know, singin' union songs or whatever
我授权你...
you have license to..
你懂吧
You know?
那 你要答应帮我介绍…
If you promise me a link-up with
当然没问题
Oh, sure. I'll... Yeah. Absolutely
好 很公平的交易
All right. Nice trade.
就这样了 对吧
This is it, huh?
他走了 他真的走了
He's gone. He's really gone
你的情绪中 高兴占了多少?
How much of you is glad?
这个嘛 我们是吵过 但是...
Well, I mean, we had our fights, okay, but.
我很想他
I miss him.
斯德哥尔摩综合征  -这个嘛…
Stockholm Syndrome.   -Well..
加上一点中国综合症
Crossed with a little bit of China Syndrome
好吧 随便
Okay, whatever.
她来了
Well, here she comes.
我就说 我能听到斑点狗的嚎叫声
Thought I could hear the sound of Dalmatians howling
我们是要 不理她 还是…
We freezing her out or what's.
不知道 已经死了一个
I don't know, one down, may be
也许 对她好一点 免得她死于心碎?
be nice in case she drops dead of a broken heart?
或是因为没心而死
Or not having a heart
当然 今天是她的大日子
True. Well, it's her big day
嗨  -嗨 亲爱的
Hi.   -Hi, darling.
你...还好吗
Are you... okay?
还好
Yep.
是吗
Yes?
是  -要命
Yes.   -Blimey.
就是说啊
I know.
真是没想到
Well, I never.
那 你…
Well, then, you..
不要紧的...
Well, well...
谢谢
Thank you?
确实
Exactly.
我们可以待会儿再谈 但是…
Well, we can get into this later, but.
你都 没想过要 告诉我吗
didn't think to let me know?
我跟你讲话 得格外小心
I have to be careful the information that I give you
免得 你拿我说的话 来对付我
because you might use it against me.
不是吗 我说错了吗  -妈
No? Am I wrong?   -Mam, mam
小可爱
Sweet one.
彼得  -你好
Peter.   -Good day
彼得超兴奋的
Peter's incredibly excited
他好像带了签名本来的
I think he's brought his autograph book
你好  -真难过
Hello.   -Oh, so sad
嗨  -真的 好难过
Hi.   -So sad
节哀  -谢了
I'm sorry.   -Thank you
爹地来了  -谢谢你
Daddy's here.   -Thank you
请节哀
Sorry for your loss.
真是遗憾  -谢谢 彼得
I'm so sorry.  -Thanks, Peter.
他常常提到你
Well, he spoke of you often
是吗  -你是他的最爱之一
Did he?   -You were one of his favorites.
我要去... 亲爱的 我要去...
I'm going to... I'm just going to, darling..
可以失陪一下吗
Would you excuse me just for one second?
他要像一只拉布拉多一样
He's now going to roll around like a Labrador
在一群参议员中打滚
in a lovely pile of senators
真尊重人家
How respectful.
那 我...  -他会来瑞典吗
Yeah. Well, then...   -Will he come to Sweden?
数据的报道开始出现了…
So, the numbers pieces are starting to come out.
没有明显的不良反应吧?
No significant blowback, right?
没有 目前为止 还挺好的
No. So far, it's... pretty good, right?
对 很好
Good. Yes.
所以 赏给红魔鬼 一颗星星
So, gold, gold star for the red devil
做得好
Good job.
你对那个 英俊的纳粹 有什么想法
Now, what are you thinking about the handsome Nazi over there?
他会赢吗
Figure he's gonna win?
疯刺的是 如果他赢了
And, if he does, like, ironically
某个高大金发的白人男性 是不是就要倒霉了
would that be bad for a tall, blond, white guy?
这整件事 都让人匪夷所思 但...
The whole thing is unimaginable, but...
如果门肯真的当选 我也想好对策了
I did have one idea, if he does come through, Mencken
我在想 与其认输
Yeah, I mean, I was wondering if it would be smart
比较聪明的做法是
rather than just to walk away
不如给他一个美国本土CEO
what about you offer him a US CEO?
是吧 只管美国境内的业务
Yeah? Just for the US properties.
让他在媒体圈拿下这一胜
Let him have that win, in the media sense.
行吗  -好
Yeah?   -Okay.
如果 我要给他一个美国本土CEO
Well, if I offer him an American CEO.
你觉得 找谁比较好呢
who, like, who would you have in mind?
我觉得 我也不知道
Oh, I mean, I don't know.
随便找个人就好
Anyone.
随便找个人啊 好  -随便找个人
Yeah. Anyone.   -Anyone.
是的 好
Yeah. Okay
我是说… 你知道该找谁吗
I mean... Actually, you know who would be good?
不知道
I don't know who would be good
小西·罗伊  -小西·罗伊
Shiv Roy.   -Shiv Roy
对  -好的
Yeah.   -Okay.
不过 她很缺经验 对吧
Very inexperienced, though, yeah?
她对政治很敏锐 了解泛美网科 可以控制叙事
Well, political acumen, knows ATN, can control the narrative.
而且头脑非常清楚
Just very, very fucking clear-sighted
而且 我还听说
Besides, I also hear, apparently
总裁 那个悲伤的瑞典人  -悲伤的瑞典人
the chairman, that sad Swede?   -The sad Swede
反正已经在控制她了
Basically pulling her strings anyway
听说 她是卢卡斯·马特森的傀儡
They say she's Lukas Mats son's total puppet.
很好
All right.
很好 你知道我听说了什么吗
All right, well, you know what I've heard?
我听说 她…
That she's..
是真的吗  -是真的
Is that true?   -Yeah, well, you know.
但她是个铁娘子
She's one of those hard bitches, right?
产假只请36小时就够了
Who's gonna do, what, 36 hours in maternity leave
剖腹产时 还能收发邮件
emailing through her vanity cesarean.
那个可怜的小孩 永远见不到她
Poor kid will never see her.
铁血女将 我懂了
A hard-ass. Okay, I get it
对 喜欢她的人不多
Yeah, not widely liked
你觉得呢
Well, what do you think?
门肯会买账吗
Would he buy it?
因为 我听说 你们两个水火不容
'Cause you two are very hate y-hate y with each other, I hear
你觉得 能让他喜欢你吗
You think you could get him to like you?
能  -真的吗
Yes.   -You think?
对  -好吧
Yeah.   -Okay.
你能帮我介绍一下吗
Can you intro?
我刚死了爹 现在什么都办得到
I can do fucking anything. My dad just died
好的 他来了
Okay. He's... he's here
他可是主角 我们过去吧
The headline act. Shall we?
好
Okay
好戏开锣了 谢谢你能来
Showtime. Thanks for comin'
应该的  -回头聊
Of course.   --We'll talk.
凯莉
Kerry?
你叫凯莉 没错吧
It is Kerry, isn't it?
对  -不是凯里 对
Yeah.   -Not Kelly. Yep
你过来跟我们坐吧
Why don't you come and sit with us?
你确定这样可以吗
Yeah... yeah, you're... you're sure that's okay?
当然 这位是谁
Absolutely. Who is this?
这是我弟弟 和我朋友
Oh, this is my brother and my friend
抱歉  -我要带她走
Sorry.   -Just going to steal her away
她跟我在一起很安全
She'll be safe with me.
我朋友是律师
My... my friend, who's a... who's a lawyer
因为 我以为
cause I thought that there might be an issue
我会进不来  -傻丫头
in terms of entry or something.   -Oh, silly
真可爱
Sweet.
你还好吗  -很好 我...
Are you all right?   -Yeah. I'm..
莎莉·安  -卡洛琳
Sally-Anne.   -Caroline
你好  -你好
Hello.   -Hello.
这位是凯莉 这位是莎莉·安
This is Kerry. Sally-Anne.
凯莉 你好  -你好
Hi, Kerry.   -Hi
来见见玛西娅
Come and meet Marcia.
对  -玛西娅 这是莎莉·安
Yes.   -Marcia, this is Sally-Anne.
你好 玛西娅  -你好
Hello, Marcia.   -Bonjour
莎莉·安是我那时候的凯莉 可以这么说
Sally-Anne was my Kerry, so to speak
那些都是过去的事了
So, it's all water under the bridge now, isn't it?
我们进去吧
Shall we go and pile in?
凯莉怎么在第一排
What is Kerry doing in the front row?
她在第一排
She's in the front row.
天啊 洛根会恨死这个场面
God, Logan would hate this.
至少他今晚不会磨牙
At least he won't grind his teeth tonight
兄弟 这是最后一通电话了
Okay, dude. This is it, final call
洛根已经装箱完毕 准备运送了
Logan is boxed and ready to be delivered
格雷格 我在”巴尔的摩”救火
Greg, there are fires in Baltimore.
达温可能会辞职 网络新闻虎视耽忧
Darwin might resign. Online i s peaking. You know?
我会尽快赶过去的 跟他们说是我
I'll get there as fast as I can. And tell them it was me.
我可以问替补扶棺的事吗  -好的
Can I inquire about front right?   -Okay.
汤姆?
Tom?
不会有事的
It's gonna be fine.
嘿 卢卡斯  -嘿 性感帅哥
Hey, hey. Hey, Lukas.   -Hey, sexy
很高兴看到你 你真好  -我也是
Nice to see you. That's very kind.   -Me too.
小西 我刚刚跟汤姆通过话
Shiv, I just spoke to Tom
看样子 他没办法来了
and it looks like he's not gonna make it
什么  -对
What?   -Yeah.
你的宝贝汤姆在哪里
Where's... Where's your Tommy boy?
在工作
He's at work.
今天新闻很多
It... Lot of news today
他在拼命工作
Yeah, he's in the grindhouse.
但 这表示 少了一个人扶棺
Sadly, that means that there's a wheel free on the casket
你们缺了一个扶棺人
You're down a wheelman
可以找彼得
Peter could take a wheel
什么  -扶棺吗 没问题
What?   -A wheel? Yes, certainly
需要人手吗
Do you need a spare pair of hands?
不不 我是说 汤姆让我替补
No, no, I was saying that Tom just kind of offered it to me
原来是这样 我误会了
Oh, I see. Tom. I misunderstood
好
Yes
不用了
No.
请起立
Please stand
慈悲的父
Into your hands, Father of Mercies
我们将洛根兄弟 托付给您
we commend our brother Logan
确信他能与所有
in the sure and certain hope
在耶稣恩慈中死亡者同在
that together with all who have died in Christ
并将在未日时 与他重生
he will rise with him on the last day
请坐 现在 我们请 最了解
Please be seated for a word
也最敬爱洛根的人 说几句话
from those who knew and loved Logan best.
格雷格…  -嘿 爷爷 嘿…
Greg...   -Hey, Gramps. Hey.
爷爷 你在做什么
What are you doing, Grandpa?
爸  -我怎么了
Dad.   -What?
别上去 这样很丢人
Don't do it. You're making a scene.
丢人的不是我 格雷格 是你
I'm not making a scene, Greg, you are.
嗨 你今天好像不用上台
Hi, I think maybe you're not on for today?
谢谢 但我一定要发言
Thank you. I'm going to speak
爷爷 能不能...
Gramps, can...
可恶  -搞什么鬼 格雷格
Fuck.   -The fuck, Greg?
你要我怎么办
What do you want me to do?
绊倒他吗?
You want me to take his legs out?
谢了
Thanks.
早安
Good morning
没关系 坐下吧  -闭嘴
It's okay, just so you know.   -Shut up.
这不是你的错 不要叫我闭嘴
It's not your fault. Don't tell me to shut up.
是什么样的人 会为了股价
What sort of people would stop a brother speaking
而阻止兄弟开口?
for the sake of a share price?
对不起
I'm sorry.
我没有立场去评断我的弟弟
It is not for me to judge my brother
他的故事 将会由历史来讲述
History will tell that story.
我只能 讲几件关于他的事情
I can just give you a couple of instances about him
各位应该都知道...
You probably all know...
我们在战争期间 为了安全 而首度来到美国
we came across the first time, during the war, for our safety
但是 我们的船 引擎故障了
But the engines of our ship let go
船队的其他船只 丢下我们
and the rest of the convoy sailed on without us
让我们随波逐流
Ieaving us adrift
他们告诉我们...
They told us..
告诉我们这些小孩…
They told us children..
如果说话
that if we spoke
咳嗽 或是稍微移动
or coughed or moved an inch
下方的U艇 会通过船壳 侦测到震动
that the U-boats would catch the vibrations through the hull
而我们 就会立即在海上丧命
and we would die in the drink, right there in the hold
我们安静了两天三夜
Three nights and two days, we stayed quiet
一个四岁的小孩 和一个五岁半的小孩
A four-year-old and a five-and-half-year-old
用眼神交谈
speaking with our eyes.
赚人热泪的故事讲完了
So, there's a little sob story.
来到美国之后 我们的叔叔
And once we were over, our uncle, who was
他算是个怪人 他…
so to speak, a character, he.
他们有一点钱…
Well, they... they had a little money
所以 把洛根送去 念一间比较好的学校
And they sent Logan a way to a better school
洛根很讨厌那里
And he hated it.
恨之入骨
He just hated it.
当时他...
He wasn't...
他身体不好 生病了
He wasn't well. He was sick
又是呻吟又是哭泣的
And he me wed and he cried
最后 他终于离开了学校
and in the end, he got out and came home
靠着自己的力量回家
under his own steam.
当他回到家
But when he got back
我们的妹妹 当时她还在襁褓之中
our little sister, she was a baby, but she was there by then..
她…
she..
他一直坚信…
He always believed..
自己把小儿麻痹症带回家了
that he brought home the polio with him
害死了妹妹
which took her
我并不知道这是不是真的
I don't even know if that's true
但是 我们的叔叔和婶婶...
But our aunt and uncle.
没有去纠正他的这个想法…
certainly did nothing to disabuse him of that notion
而是让它 在洛根心里 发酵
They let it lie with him.
我想...我是爱他的
I... loved him, I suppose.
我想 你们有些人 也是爱他的
And I suppose some of you did, too.
以 他愿意的程度
In whatever way he would let us
和 我们可以接受的方式 去爱他
and we could manage.
但是...我忍不住要说…
But... I can't help but say..
他做了一些糟糕透顶的事情
he has wrought the most terrible things
他曾经 限缩了世界的边缘
He was a man who has here and there drawn in the edges of the world
他曾经 为天空带来阴霾
Now and then darkened the skies a little.
封闭了人心
Closed men's hearts
助长了人们心中 黑暗的火焰
Fed that dark flame in men.
那冷硬 恶毒 无情的火焰
The hard, mean, hard-relenting flame
温暖了自己的家 但是让别人受冻
that keeps their hearts warm while another grows cold
自己储粮 让别人挨饿
their grain stashed while another goes hungry
甚至 还有脸说着 无良 但好笑...
and even has the temerity to tell that hard funny,
对 好笑…
yes, funny..
但无良的笑话 取笑受冻的人
but hard joke about the man in the cold.
温暖舒适的人 当然可以趾高气昂
You can get a little high, a little mighty, when you're warm.
对 他从数十亿身家中捐了几百万出去
Oh yes, he... he gave away a few million of his billions
但 他并不是一个慷慨的人
but he was not a generous man.
他很刻薄
He was mean.
世界观也很刻薄
And he made but a mean estimation of the world.
助长了人性中的贫乏
And he fed a certain kind of meagerness in men.
也许 他是不得不然
Perhaps he had to.
因为 他自己也很贫乏
Because he had a meagerness about him
也许 我也是
And maybe I do about me, too
我不知道
I don't know.
我尽力了
I try.
我不知道是何时发生的
I don't know when..
但 他决定不再尽力了
but some time, he decided not to try anymore
这是莫大的耻辱
And it was a terrible shame.
一路好走 弟弟…
Godspeed, my brother...
愿上帝保佑你
and God bless.
是啦…
Yeah..
你还好吗
You okay?
你会说些爸爸的好话吧?
You're gonna... you're gonna say the other side. Yeah?
那不是爸爸的全部 对吧
Like, that's... that's not it. That's not everything, right?
对 我很好 我很好
Yeah. I'm good, I'm good.
我上台时 可能会挑逗一下玛西娅
I might hit on Marcia on the way up
你没问题的
Yep. Here goes.
孩子 你还好吗
You okay, son?
还好 我已经先伤心过了 而且我不是你的孩子
Yeah, I pre-grieved. Not your son.
你讲的很精彩 也很无情
It was a good hard take that you gave
等一下
One second
我…
My
我父亲 洛根·罗伊
My father, Logan Roy, was.
好…
Right.
他是个伟人…
He was a... a great man in the...
不折不扣的"微”…  “微人” 是伟人
in the true sense... sense of the world... word
可恶
Fuck.
你们上来
Guys, come here.
不
Yeah, no.
我不能...我没办法
So, I can't do the... I can't... I can't do the thing
我做不到 我真的不行
I actually can't do... I can't
我试过了 但是不行  -冷静一下
I tried the thing and I just can't.   -Just take a second.
没关系 深吸一口气
It's okay. Just take a breath
嘿  -没事的 深呼吸…
Hey.   --It's okay, it's okay. Just take...
他真的在里面吗
Is he... is he in there?
对  -对
Yeah.   -Yeah.
可以让他出来吗
Get... get him out.
嘿 没事的  -没事的
Hey... it's okay.   -It's okay
没事的
It's okay.
对不起
And I'm sorry
没事的 嘿 嘿
It's okay. Hey, hey
深吸一口气  -没事的 你没事的
Just take a breath.   -Hey, it's okay. You're okay
有我们在
We got you, okay?
你要去讲吗
Do you wanna..
我...  -好 肯 你能...
-I...   -Yeah. Ken, will you..
收到 我觉得... 因为你要...
Yeah, yeah, I think it's...'Cause you gotta...
你要讲爸爸的另一面
You gotta say the other side
而不是...  -我能行 我能行
It's not, you know. Yeah.   -I got it, I got it
我来照顾他 我来照顾他  -你照顾他?
I got him, I got him.   -You got him?
对  -对不起
Yeah.   -Sorry.
没关系 我去...  -对不起 我真是笨死了
It's okay. I'l I just...   -Oh, it's stupid. I'm sorry
你们有笔吗 有没有人带笔?
Do you guys have a pen?
没有  -我有
No, -Yeah, yeah. Here.
对不起...对不起
I'm sorry that... I'm sorry.
没关系  -对 没关系
No, it's okay.   -Yeah, it's okay.
有我在 没问题  -你可以…好
I got you. I got you.   -You do... You got... Okay
谢谢
Thank you.
请等我一下
Just bear with me a second, please
我要试着 代替我弟 说几句话
I'm gonna try to just stand in for my brother.
我喝点水就好了
I think I just need water or something
嘿 雨果 去拿瓶水来好吗
Hey, Hugo. Can you get some fucking water?
没问题  -我这里有他的稿子
Of course.   -I have some of his words
我妹妹和兄弟的 但是...
my sister's and my brother's, but..
我不确定自己知道多少
Yeah, I don't know how much I know
但是 我了解我父亲
but... I knew my father.
我自己就 说过…
You know, I... I've said it, I said it..
我曾说过的 和我伯伯讲得 也都没错
And it is true, what I said, what my uncle said
对 我父亲...
Yeah? My father was.
很残忍
a brute.
他很强硬
He was, he was tough
但他 也建造了...
But also, he built..
行动了
and he acted.
有很多人 总会跟你说不行
And there are many people out there who will always tell you no.
因为 有上千个理由... 他们永远有理由
And there are a thousand reasons. There... I mean, there always are
永远 有上千个 不行动的理由
A thousand reasons not to. To not act
但他 不是那种人
But he was never one of those.
他有…
He had a..
你们知道的 他有一股生命力
You know, he had a vitality
有一股 会伤人的力量
a force that could hurt
他确实伤了不少人
And it did
但是 天啊 那种十足的...
But, my god, the sheer, the..
你们看看 他塑造的生命
I mean, look at it, the lives and the livings..
生计 和事物
and the things that he made.
还有金钱
And the money
对 金钱
Yeah. The money
金钱是氧气和命脉
The lifeblood, the oxygen of this... this
供养了我们从无到有 打造的这个 美好文明
this wonderful civilization that we have built from the mud
金钱就是赋予生命的血球
The money, the corpuscles of life
奔流贯穿这个国家 和全世界
gushing around this nation, this world
让世间男女心中 充满了欲望
filling men and women all around with... with desire.
刺激了 拥有打造 交易 获利
Quickening the ambition to own and make and trade and profit
建造 和改良的 野心
and build and improve.
他用意志力 创造了生命的涌泉
I mean, great geysers of life he willed..
创造了 屹立不摇的高楼大厦
of buildings he made stand
创造了 船舰 钢铁 船壳
of ships, steel hulls
娱乐 报纸 节目 电影 和生命
amusements, newspapers, shows, and films, and life
复杂得要命的生命
Bloody, complicated life.
他让生命得以发生
He made life happen.
他创造了我 和我的三位手足
He made me and my three siblings
抱歉
Sorry.
对 他有一种骇人的力量
And... and yes, he had a terrible force to him
和 会压人的 凶猛野心
and a fierce ambition that could push you to the side
但是 那也只是人性
But... But it was only that... that human thing
是存在被看见和行动的意志
the will to be and to be seen and to do.
现在有人也许会想扭曲他的回忆
And now people might want to tend and prune the memory of him
想诋毁抹黑那股力量
to denigrate that force.
他那股 宏伟骇人的力量
That magnificent, awful force of him,
但 老天 希望我也有这股力量
but my god, I hope it's in me.
因为 若是我们少了他那股精力
Because if we can't match his vim
天晓得 未来会多么萎靡和单调
then God knows the future will be sluggish and gray
不论是在
You know, there was n't a room
向他请益的议事厅
from the grandest state room where his advice was sought
还是在播放他的新闻的简朴民宅
to the lowest house where his news played
他都能怡然自处
where he couldn't walk and wasn't comfortable.
他在这个世界非常自在
He was comfortable with this world
而且 他心里有数
And he knew it.
他心里有数 他甘之如饴
He knew it and he liked it.
所以 我敬佩他
And I say amen to that
说得好
That was great. There's a...
还有办公室那段  -好
The bit about the office.   -Yeah. Okay.
真的很抱歉 对不起 我实在...  -没关系
Sorry about that. Sorry. It just...   -It's okay
没关系  -你说得很棒
It's okay.   -That was good
你说得很棒  -谢谢
That was good.   -Thank you
今天这样的状况
So, the... the way things have gone today
让我们没有机会...
we have n't had a chance to.
罗曼 没关系的 还有 谢谢你 肯 你说的
And it's okay, Rome. And thank you, Ken, that was
我们还有话没有说完 所以 我要补充一下
Yeah, but we haven't said everything and so, I'm just gonna...
很快就说完了 抱歉
It will be done so on. Sorry.
我父亲...
My father..
我们以前 会在他办公室外面玩耍
We... we used to play outside his office
我想 大概是想让他听到吧
and I... I think because we wanted him to hear.
他从办公室出来的时候 好可怕
And he would come out, and he was so terrifying
他...
He was..
天啊 我们被他吓死了
Oh god, he was so terrifying to us
他会出来大吼 叫我们安静
He'd come out, and he'd... he'd yell at us to be quiet
像是...“不要吵”
You know, this... this, " Silence!"
他在办公室里做的事情很重要
And what he was doing in there was so important
我们无法想像那是什么事
we couldn't conceive of... of what it was
总统 国王 女王 外交官
You know, presidents and kings and queens and diplomats
首相 和世界银行家
and prime ministers and world bankers
我也不知道 他…
And I don't know. Yeah, he...
他把我们拒之门外
He kept us outside.
但是 他对任何人都是如此
But he kept everyone outside.
但是...他接纳你时...
But... when he let you in.
阳光普照的时候
when the sun shone..
就很温暖
it was warm.
在阳光中 真的好温暖
Yeah, it was really... it was warm in the light.
但是 做他的女儿很难
But it was hard to be his daughter
我不能不
I can't not..
你知道 他…
You know, he was, it was.
他对女人很严格
Oh, he was hard on women.
他的脑中 容不下完整的女人
You know, he couldn't, he couldn't fit a whole woman in his head
但他做得还不错
But he did okay.
你做得还不错 爸爸
You did okay, Dad.
我们都在这里 也都好好的
We're all here, and we're doing okay
我们都好好的
We're doing okay.
所以 永别了
So, goodbye..
我至亲至爱的父亲
my dear, dear, world of a father.
请起立
Please stand
全能的主啊
And we pray. Almighty God
祈祷您的仆人 洛根·罗伊
that your servant Logan
离开尘世
may journey from this world...
阿门
Amen.
谢了 杰西
Thanks, Jess.
谢谢.
Thank you..
嘿 很高兴见到你 很高兴见到你
Hey, good to see you, good to see you.
嘿 谢谢
Hey. Thank you
你讲得太好了  -谢谢
That was perfect.   -Thank you.
晚点聊?  -好的
Talk later?   -Yes.
太感谢了 谢谢
Thanks so much. Thank you
保重  -谢谢
Take care.   -Thank you
待会儿详细跟你说 但我刚刚跟艾芭谈过
We'll fill you in later, but very interesting conversation. Ebba.
小西说 要找个美国本土CEO来安抚门肯
Shiv floating a US CEO to placate Mencken.
看看那个玩意儿 天啊
Look at that thing. Jesus
他没有传照片给你们吗 你们没有看过?
He never sent you pictures? You never saw this?
有吗 我没看过
Did he? No, I... I never saw this
你们呢  -没有
Did you guys?   -No.
没错 他付了很划算的价钱
Yeah. He got it on a deal
天啊  -他那时很满意
Oh, man.   -He was really pleased
据我所知...
It was a..
这是一个网络宠物用品商 建造的
It was a dot com pet supply guy who built it, I believe
什么  -但那个人后来不想要了
What?   -But that guy decided against.
对 是的  -真的吗 你是说真的?
Yeah. Yeah.   -Really? Are you serious?
他跟斯大林和利伯拉契竞标吗
Was he in a bidding war with Stalin and Liberace?
是不是
Right?
爸...
Pop sort of.
我想 他是不愿意入土
I think he didn't wanna go in the ground
我认为 他不愿意多想这件事
And I think he didn't wanna think about it too much
所以 在拍卖会上买了这个 就这样了
so I think he just went in for it at auction and, boom.
猫食奥兹曼迪亚斯
Cat food Ozymandias.
他好像一口气花了五百万
I think it was five mill all in.
但 可以永久使用这间墓室
But that's forever.
对  -当然了
Yeah.   -Obviously.
五百万?
Five mill?
真划算  -对
Good deal.   -Yeah
来 我带你们参观
Come on, I'll show you round.
这里可以抵税吗 因为严格说起来 这算住宅?
Is it also a tax write-off? 'Cause it's technically a residence?
是啊
Yeah.
你有兴趣?
You interested?
是啊 有机会了解他
Yeah, a chance to get to know him?
我得去跟威拉谈谈
I'll have to talk to Willa
我死后 本来想冷冻保存 但是…
I was crazy for cryogenics, but yeah.
有机会睡上铺 我也不会拒绝
I wouldn't say no to a top bunk
你呢
You?
我不知道
Man, I don't know.
是啊
Yeah.
我连跟他喝杯酒都有困难
I had trouble finishing a Scotch with him.
那会让我呼吸困难
He made me breathe funny
…拭去我们眼中的泪
...and wipe away every tear from our eyes
以 圣父 圣子 和圣灵之名
In the name of the Father and of the Son and of the Holy Spirit
阿门
Amen.
弥撒礼成
Go in the peace of Christ.
我很想看他这次 如何脱身
You know, I'm intrigued to see how he gets out of this one
天啊 我受不了了 受不了了
Man. Oh, it's too much, it's too much
爸不是真的...
Dad wasn't really.
爸爸…到底有多坏?
How... How bad was Dad?
他是个暴躁的老家伙 真的
He was a salty dog. He was
但 他是个好人
But he was a good egg
是个表里如一的人
What you saw was what you got
是吗
Yeah?
没错
Yeah
好
Okay.
对吧
Right?
你还好吗
You okay?
还好 你呢
Yeah. You?
我很爱他 也很想他
I loved him very much. I miss him very much
他伤了我的心
He broke my heart
也伤了你们的心
and he broke your hearts, too
大雨 还好吗
Big H. How you doing?
谁 在下吗?
Who? Little old me?
我很好 今天是大日子
I'm fine. You know. Big day.
对
Yeah.
过来 听着
Come here. Listen.
有事要交给你去办
I got something for you
我要你 对媒体说明背景
I want you to brief media on background
你找我 就算找对人了
Then I am the droid you are looking for
就说 马特森的并购案
Okay? That Mats son's acquisition
没有得到家族重要成员的支持
doesn't have the support of key members of the family
但 不要指名道姓
But you don't say who.
马特森想用贱价买下这间公司
Mats son's trying to steal the company for a song
董事会开始对交易失去兴趣
Board is souring on the deal.
他们的看法是 生活+ 等等
Okay, the feeling is, you know, Living Plus, et cetera
大选后 价格攀升 泛美网科声势看涨…
the price soaring post-election, ATN pumped
韦斯达的价格被低估 溢价过低
under values Way star, premium's too low.
明白
Got it.
明白吗  -明白了
Got it?   -Yeah
雨果 人生并不美好
You know, Hugo, life isn't nice.
充满了不确定性
It's contingent.
说爱你的人 也会恶整你
People who say they love you also fuck you.
所以 这个计划是要让交易破产
So, this is an explicit plan to fuck the deal
由我统治全世界
me rule the world
你可以跟着来
And you can come
但 这不是合作关系 好吗
but it won't be a collaboration, okay?
你将是我养的狗
You'll be my dog.
但 狗吃的剩菜 价值高达数百万
But the scraps from the table will be millions.
好几百万
Millions.
满意吗
Happy?
汪 汪
wang wang
他来了
There he is.
大个子 你好吗
How you doing, big man?
是啊
Yeah
你怎么样
How are you doing yourself?
这阵子可好?
You okay these days?
很好啊
Sure.
因为我听说 你去做心理咨询?
Cause I hear you were talking to a head shrinker
那应该是保密的
Supposed to be confidential
好吧 对不起
All right, well, I'm sorry.
抱歉 但 这恐怕是公开的秘密
Sorry, but I'm afraid it's not.
没关系的 只不过
I mean, that's cool. It's cool. It's just..
人言可畏
People talk.
我最近很闲 所以...
I got time on my hands, so.
对
Yeah.
告诉你 我的想法
Yeah, I tell.. I tell you what I think
我觉得 你可以来为我工作
I think you come work for me.
像你这样魁梧的大个子
Like, big strong guy like you? What are you fucking..
去做什么咨询啊?
What are you fucking gab bling about, huh?
我并不喜欢  -是的 我知道...
I don't love it.   -No, I... No, I know..
我并不喜欢  -我也不喜欢
I don't love it.   -Me neither, me neither.
来为我工作
Come work for me
想来就跟我说  -好
Talk to me.   -Okay.
想来就说话
Talk to me. Yeah
很好
Good.
好家伙
Good man.
一向如此
Always, always.
肯  -怎么了
Ken.   -Yeah.
门肯来了
Mencken is here.
想看我一头栽进他的鬼话吗
You wanna watch me scuba in his bullshit?
我想…
I guess, what
等痛苦的法律程序走完
Sort of like congratulations
就可以恭喜你了吧?
pending a grueling jurisdictional knife fight
对吗  -对 我很有信心
Yeah?   -Yeah. No, no. Confident
真令人兴奋  -确实
Exciting. It's exciting.   -It is.
听说你在找人
I hear you're harvesting names.
肯顿?  -对
Kenton?   -Exactly, yes.
对吗  -给肯顿就好
Yeah?   -Give them to Kenton.
多谢  -小事一件
Many thanks.   -Yeah, no worries.
我想...
So, yeah, I gues...
有鉴于我们手上现有的资料
Given what we have, you know, on our side, you know...
还有基于共有的愿景 而高度合作的意向
how we've been pleased to cooperate in terms of shared vision
我想跟你聊聊
I guess I wanted to touch base.
找时间 交流一下 让你知道我的想法
Wanted to talk, chat, get my thoughts to you
我以为你只负责音响系统
Oh, I thought you were the sound system.
现在 要选歌了?
Now you wanna choose the track
不是 我...  -对 我是说…
No, I...  --Yeah, no, I mean..
这不是单向道
Not one-way traffic
明白
All right.
就是...
Like...
我想问问 你打算何时
I don't know, when might you be dropping something publicly
公开提出 你在法规方面的疑虑
about your regulatory concerns
就是 不想让黑心的海外科技公司 收购伟大的美国企业
vis-a-vis big bad foreign tech and great American corporations?
好 我说过 我会想办法帮忙的
Right. Well, I've said I'll try to help
“想办法帮忙" ?   -先生 你好
" Try to help "?   -Hello, sir.
在下格雷格·赫许  -嗨
Greg Hirsch.   -Hi.
是汤姆在泛美网科的同事  -格雷格 格雷格
ATN with Tom.   -Greg, Greg
这个人跟我很熟
This guy knows me well.
恭喜您  -谢谢
Congratulations.   -Thank you.
汤姆和我 很荣幸 昨晚能为您效力...
Tom and I were proud to be pull in'for you last night for..
但是 汤姆率先决定要宣布...  -嘿 笨蛋
But, yeah, Tom called it...   -Hey, hey, stupid
并且 由我转达  -滚开 好吗 谢了
And I relayed the call, so...   -Fuck off, okay? Thanks
有多远滚多远  -嘿
Why don't you piss off.   -Hey...
一边待着去  -爱哭包来了 小眼泪
Take a hike.   -It's the Grim Weeper. Tiny Tear
逗你的 你还好吧
Kidding. You good?
嘿 今天客气点 好吗,  -没事
Hey, be easy today. Yeah?   -It's fine.
嘿 杰哥 你好吗  -你好吗
Hey, J Man. Hey.   -Hi. What's up?
你好吗 嘿 我就是想
How are you do in'? Hey, just wanted t...
嘿 谢谢 我想占用五分钟...  -康
Hey, thanks. Wanted to grab five just to...   -Con.
别担心 是好事 没问题的
No, no, it's copacetic. It's cool
我只想占用五分钟谈谈
I just want to grab five, you know
谈谈”花小钱去斯洛文尼亚”的事
just to talk macro Slovenia, micro travel budget
康 别说了
Con, Con.
我想跟同僚提出一些我的想法
I'm trying to talk with my colleague to bat some ideas
若我提出
Like, what if I said to you
由美国带领的 泛哈布斯堡 替代欧盟的组织
pan-Habsburg, American-led EU alternative?
你会怎么说
What would you say to me?
打扰一下 总统先生  -小西 小西
Excuse me, Mr. President?   -Shiv, Shiv
请跟我来 我是您的撤离小组
If you care to follow me, I'm your extraction team.
失陪了  -我们正在...
Excuse me.   -We're just having a.
也许您想跟马特森先生谈谈
Perhaps you'd like to chat with Mr. Mats son.
当然 应该的
Oh. Sure. I guess so.
祝您好运 总统先生  -因为 我想说的是…
Good luck, Mr. President.   -'Cause my thing is.
你知道”超级妈妈”的计划吗
You know about Super mom's plan?
不知道  -也许该开放
No.   -Maybe it's time to open up.
让大家进大帐棚了
Big tent this shit.
我不欢迎某些龟孙子进大帐棚
Some motherfuckers I don't want in the tent.
这我知道 他在这里
No, I know that. I... Well, here we go.
欢迎  -也许我们...
Val kommen.   -Okay, perhaps we..
我要你去打听 这件事的走向
All right, I need you to find out where this goes
和结果 好吗  -没问题
and how it lands, okay?   -Got it.
瞧瞧我们
Okay, well, look at us.
金发 红发 和棕发人 走进酒吧
A blonde, a brunette, and a redhead walk into the bar
自由派 保守派 和...
Liberal, conservative, and whatever
你奉行什么哲学?
What... what's your philosophy exactly?
隐私 女人 和意大利面
Privacy pussy pasta.
无政府资本主义 和帕马森芝士
Anarcho-capitalist parmigiana.
恭喜  -谢谢
So, congratulations.   -Thank you
真令人兴奋  -是啊
Very exciting stuff.   -Yeah.
我们都很忙 所以 我长话短说
Yeah, I'm gonna keep this brief 'cause we're both quite busy
但 我…
But I..
我要韦斯达
I want Way star.
新闻我也要分一杯羹 包括体育
I want a piece of the news, I want sports
档案 数据库 知识产权 人才 这些好东西 我都要
Archive, library, IP, talent, all that good stuff.
我真的很想做成这笔交易
And I... I really like the deal.
我们想谈谈
So, what we would wanna talk about is
你要怎么才能...前提是 你不阻挡这笔交易
what would make you assuming you make it
你要怎样才能放心的让他拥有这家公司?
what would reassure you about his ownership?
我要先声明
Okay, I just wanna be frank about
让你放心 是我非常重视的事
how important it is for me that you feel comfortable about this
是这样的...不管我们之间有哪些冲突
I guess... No, no, the thing was... whatever our frictions
我跟令尊之间 一向存在着意识形态上的同理心
there was an ideological sympathy with your dad
我父亲的腹中是波涛涵涌
My dad had deep ocean currents swirling in his gut
但是 说到细节
But I think on specifics
他注重的是金钱 获胜 和八卦
he was about money, winning, and gossip
说到GoJo 和GoJo社群媒体
Well, in terms of, like, across Go Jo and Go Jo socials
和各种通讯环境之类的
and all the kind of communication environment, whatever..
现在的情况是 我们生产的东西 人人都有
We're in this place where we are making the thing that everyone has
但没人知道运作原理
but nobody knows how it works.
而且 这个领域的意见领袖
Okay? And there's a very small number of people
少之又少
that are thought leaders in that space.
我在想 也许您会想听听我们的理念
And so, I just think that maybe you might wanna hear our take
您明白吗
You know?
而且 还蛮好玩的
It... it's also kind of fucking fun.
所以 你可以掌握几个小喽啰
So, it's either a couple of tiny men in your pocket
或是开启通往广泛文化影响力的门户
or a gateway to broad and growing cultural influence.
重点是 法规的架构
Well, you know, it's really all about regulatory framework
海外投资委员会的考量 所以 去他的
CFIUS considerations, so yeah, muck about that.
那个我管不了 国家利益和国内...
It would be out of my hands, national interest and domestic..
当然 我只想说…
Of course. Can I... Can I just say that..
我感兴趣的那些东西
Like, the stuff that I'm interested in
我不用介入日常营运
there's no need for me to be deep inside it on a day-to-day basis
所以 举例而言
So, for example
我只是随口说说 但也许 可以找个美国本土CEO
just spit balling here, may be an American CEO?
这样也许 比较不会触犯 文化上的禁忌
Would that help make things feel a bit more culturally aligned?
有没有可能?  -什么
Perhaps?   -Oh, what?
这位女士吗?
Kinder, Kuche, Kirche over here?
我还以为你讨厌我
I thought you hated me.
我父亲很有弹性 我也是 我很识时务的
My dad was flexible, I'm flexible. I know how things go
他胜选 你会很高兴 对吧
And... you would be very glad, right? To see him win.
我高兴与否 不重要
My feelings are irrelevant.
重点是 我们的观众喜欢杰瑞德
Our audience loves Jeryd,
而我 尊重我们的观众
and so, I respect our audience.
我爱你们的观众
And I love your audience.
俄亥俄  -好
Ohio.   -Oh, all right
跟你们聊得很愉快
Good talk.
祝你在俄亥俄一切顺利  -聊得很愉快
Have fun with Ohio.   -Great chat.
你终于决定来了
Decided to turn up
对 我只能待20分钟
Yeah. I can only stay for 20
外面变得有点像天安门
It's getting a bit Tiananmen-y out there.
真有种 全新的汤姆啊
Ballsy. Jesus, a whole new Tom.
要是爸还活着
You would never have dared
你绝对不敢不来参加他的葬礼
not to come to his funeral when he was alive
对 问题是 过去这几天
Yeah, well, the thing about your dad is that
你父亲失去了不少影响力
he's lost quite a lot of influence over the past few days
对
Yeah.
谢谢
Thank you.
等一下
Excuse me?
没关系的 没关系的
Yeah, it's fine. It's fine.
我知道 没关系
I know it's fine.
所以...
So...
所以  -说啊
So.   -What?
说什么
What?
你要解释发生了什么事吗
Are you going to explain? Ever? To me? What happened?
为什么你没有...还有整件事的经过
Why you didn't... and how.
经过?  -对
And how?   -Yeah.
我也没有心理准备
I mean, I wasn't expecting it
我先是不确定要不要留着
Yeah, I mean, I wasn't sure that I wanted to keep it
又不确定胎儿健不健康
Then I wasn't sure that it was okay
但后来得知胎儿很健康
But it turns out that, by all accounts, it is
你为什么不告诉我?  -所以...
So, why didn't you tell me?   -So.
因为 感觉很可悲 汤姆
Because it seemed so sad, Tom.
我们当时...还在蜜月期
And... And we were in... a honeymoon phase and.
对  -对
Yep.   -Yeah.
带潜在的爸爸去试车
Taking the potential dad for a test drive.
去你的
Oh, fuck you.
这对快乐的小夫妻  -嘿
Hello there, happy couple.   -Hey
恭喜 汤姆  -谢谢
Congratulations, Tom.   -Hi. Oh, thank you
非常感谢  -恭喜 汤姆 真是好消息
Thank you so much. Yeah.   -Lovely news
做得好  -可惜 这是一场大灾难
Well done, you.   -Well, if it wasn't such a total fuckin'disaster
不然 还真是美梦成真
it would be a dream come true.
我相信 一定会很棒的
Well, I'm sure it will be wonderful
你还好吗 小西
Are you all right about it, Shiv?
当妈妈很难
I mean, it's hard
不会 我会遵循家族的做法
Oh, no, I'm not gonna see it.
应该不会跟宝宝见到面
I'm just gonna do it the family way
对 对  -是啊
Oh, right, right.   -Yeah
那样就好 如果见不到孩子就没问题
Oh, that'll work fine. If you don't see it, that's fine.
对 他们的感情发展不会受到影响吧
Yeah, I mean, they don't grow up emotionally stunted, do they?
应该不会 你觉得呢
I shouldn't think so. What do you think?
卡洛琳 亲爱的  -失陪
Caroline? Darling?   -Oh, sorry
抱歉
Sorry.
杀了我吧
Fuck me.
你妈妈真是的
Your mom.
你很快就会学着抽离
You learn to disassociate fairly early
嘿 我想...
Hey, I wanna...
过来
Come here.
我想...说声对不起
I wanna... I wanna say sorry..
因为我没有陪着你
for not being there
因为我...
'Cause I.
我很想来
I wanted to have been and.
但你知道 我累得要命
But, I, you know, I'm so, so tired and I have...
因为好久没有睡觉了 而且...
I've been awake for so, so long and I..
觉得自己不能离开
just felt I couldn't leave.
你懂吗  -没关系
You know?   -Yeah. It's okay
没事
Fine.
我当时是第一个进去陪他的人
And, you know, I was... I was the first one in there with him.
在他死后
After he died.
真的
I was.
所以 我...
So, I did say...
我跟他道别过了
I did say goodbye to him
真的  -那好
I did.   -Okay.
很好
Good.
你累坏了
You're exhausted
嘿 不如这样...
Hey, why don't... why don't you.
你回我们的公寓
Why don't you back to the apartment?
我不能去...  -去睡几个小时
I can't...   -For a couple of hours
就睡一会儿
Just, you know, sleep
你确定?  -我不在乎
Sure?   -I don't care.
旅馆的人认识我 我很受不了
The people at the hotel know me, and I... I hate it.
我不喜欢
I don't like it.
去躲一会儿
Just hide out for a while.
好 谢谢
Okay. Thank you
答案是“好”  -好?
It's a yes.   -Yes?
对
Yes.
你是说...是吗?
From... Yeah?
对
Yeah.
好
Okay.
这招好
Great move.
很聪明  -对他们很有兴趣
Smart.   -Yeah. I think they're interested
而且
And...
我应该可以让他们接受美国本土CEO
I think I can make a US CEO work
太好了 咱们...
Great. Let's..
咱们来做肉丸汉堡吧
Let's make a meatball burger
对
Yeah
晚安  -好
Good night.   -Okay.
嘿 兄弟  -你好
Hey, bud.   -Hey a.
你还好吗
Are you okay?
你看她 穿着高跟鞋的样子
Look at her. In her fucking pomp.
容光焕发
She's fucking glowing
志得意满 蓄势待发
All dope, one in the chamber.
听我说 我可能需要你帮忙 兄弟
Yeah. Listen, I might need your help, bro
卢卡斯 和小西
Lukas and Shiv.
可能...他们可能 跟门肯谈好了
It's possible... There might be an accommodation with Mencken.
跟你的好哥们  -不可能
With your pal.   -No, no
真的  -不可能 我们说好了的
Yeah.   -No, we have an agreement
他会阻止这笔交易
and, you know, he's gonna block the deal
我们现在筹码不多 好吗
We don't have a lot of leverage at this point, right?
所以 我们可能要出一些招
So, we might need to... to make some moves.
我也需要请你帮忙
And I might need your help.
我现在
I don't...
我现在状况不太好
I don't really feel so great at the moment
我知道 我知道
Yeah, I know. I know.
对不起
Sorry.
那是因为你搞砸了
That's because you fucked it.
天啊 你在说什么  -没关系 这种事 难免的
Jesus, man. What the fuck?   -No, it's okay, man. It's okay.
听我说 这种事很正常
Look, it happens, it happens
你自以为跟爸一样 想用爸的方式蛮干
You thought you were Dad, shot your Dad bit.
我的天啊 别这么咄咄逼人 该死的
Holy shit, dude. Take it easy. Fuck
跟杰瑞德的事情 你搞砸了  -不 我没有搞砸
Yeah, you fucked it with Jeryd.   -No, I didn't fuck it
我没有搞砸 因为如果他想食言
No, I didn't, because, you know, if he tries to, you know
不去阻止这笔交易
welch on the deal or whatever to block then..
我们掌握了他的要害 我们可以伤害他
you know, we got him, we can fuckin'hurt him.
我们有泛美网科
We have... we have ATN
知道吧?  -这个嘛 对
-You know?   -Right. Well, yeah
所以 我没有搞砸 好吗  -他捏住了我们的要害
So, I didn't fuck it, okay?   -He's got our dick in his hand
我们也该捏住他的要害
We should have his dick in our hand
好 我不...好吧  -对吧
I... I don't... Okay.   -Yeah?
我想…
I think...
我们有吗?
We do?
我该阻止的 所以我很自责
I should've stopped it so I'm blaming myself
但 现在要靠我们了 老弟
but it's on us, dude, okay?
如果不想放开韦斯达
We don't wanna say bye-bye to Way star?
我们必须在董事会上跟小西对抗
We have to get fuckin' real and fight Shiv at the board
罗伊兄弟 对上小西本人
The Roy Boys versus Shiv the Shiv.
好吗
Okay?
没事 有我在就行了
It's okay. I mean, I've got it.
我有计划 但是需要你帮忙
I have a plan, but I'm gonna need you to just...
你帮我吗
Yeah? Help me here?
我们可以的 兄弟
And we can do this. Okay, dude?
好吗 你搞砸了 但是没关系
Okay? You fucked it, but it's all right.
你收到了吗 你收到了吗  -什么 没有
Did you get this? Did you get it?   -What? No
我寄给你  -什么
I'll send it to you.   -What?
是谁录的
Who recorded it?
我想… 应该是雷
I think... I think it was Ray
你们听 他听起来 活像一头
Listen to this, he sounds like a sow
待宰的母猪  -是罗曼吗
that's about to get the stun gun and knows it.   -Rome?
这是在开玩笑吗
You're kidding me
不 视频已经传开了
No, this is circulating
不要播放  -别这样
Don't play that.   -Come on, guys.
这是力量的展现 反正已经传开了
A show of strength. It's circulating!
太过分了
Oh, that's not right
我用走的 谢谢 谢谢
I'm... I'm walk in'. Thank you, thank you.
很好 老天爷啊
Great. Jesus Christ
嘿 别走那边 第五大道人太多了
Hey, I wouldn't go that way. It's a bull run over on 5th
好 继续加油
Okay, well, keep up the good work, okay?
瞧这些人
Fucking kidding me
去你的
Fuck you.
回家啦 回家啦 你去死  -你去死吧
Go home, go home. Fuck you.   -Fuck you, dude
你叫我去死? 你去死 你这个烂人
Oh, fuck me? Fuck you! Fuck you, you piece of shit!
你们什么都不懂
No fucking idea!
什么都不懂 一群白痴
No idea! Morons!
白痴 屁都不懂的呆子
Idiots. Fuckin' morons, all of you.
你是个蠢到极点的白痴 什么都不懂
You're a stupid fucking idiot. You have no fucking idea.
让开  -什么都不懂的白痴
Dude, move.   -None. Idiot. Morons.
去死吧你
Go fuck yourself!
蠢到极点  -去死吧
Stupid fuckers.   -Fuck you, man
你才去死 傻逼
Oh, fuck you, you piece of shit
滚开
Get the fuck outta here
别碰我 傻逼
Don't fucking touch me, you piece of shit